Guide to the National Lawyers Guild Records TAM.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Part 2, Series VIII: NLG v. AG - Discovery, 1921-1987
  - Subseries F: Released Government Documents, National Lawyers Guild Individuals.
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1940-1966 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1943-1966 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [I], 1944-1966 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [II], 1944-1966 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1944-1974 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1944-1977 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1945-1965 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1945-1969 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1945-1970 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [I], 1948-1967 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [II], 1948-1967 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1948-1973 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [I], 1948-1975 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [II], 1948-1975 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1949-1952 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1949-1956 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1949-1963 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1949-1967 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [I], 1949-1969 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [II], 1949-1969 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1950-1956 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [I], 1950-1966 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References [II], 1950-1966 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1950-1971 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References, 1951 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Crockett, George W., Jr.: See References (Part 5, Field Offices), 1974-1978 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 1 of 14): HQ 100-466871, Vol. 1, Feb 1969-Oct 1971 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 1 of 14): HQ 100-466371, Vol. 1, Oct 1971-Feb 1972 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 2 of 14): HQ 100-466371, Vol. 2, EBF 79, Mar 1972-Jan 1977 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 3 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 1, Sep 1969-Jan 1971 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 4 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 2, Jan 1971-Apr 1971 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 4 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 2, Apr 1971-Jul 1971 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 5 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 3, Jul 1971-Sep 1971 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 5 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 3, Sep 1971-Oct 1971 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 6 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 4, Oct 1971-Dec 1971 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 7 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 5, Dec 1971-Feb 1972 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 8 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 6, Feb 1972-May 1972 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 8 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 6, May 1972-Aug 1972 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 9 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 7, Sep 1972-Jun 1973 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 9 of 14): CG 100-46511, Vol. 7, Jun 1973-Mar 1975 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 10 of 14): Various Case Numbers, Aug 1971-Nov 1974 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 10 of 14): BU 100-21778, Vol. 1, Nov 1971-Jun 1972 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 10 of 14): BU 100-21778, Vol. 1, Jun 1972-Jan 1975 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 11 of 14): BU 100-21778, Vol. 2, Jun 1975-Jun 1977 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 11 of 14): Various Case Numbers, Aug 1971-Nov 1974 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 12 of 14): Various Case Numbers, Sep 1971-Jun 1972 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 12 of 14): NY 100-173632, Jun 1971-Mar 1975 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 13 of 14): Various Case Numbers, Aug 1971-Feb 1975 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 14 of 14): SF 100-70695, Jun 1971-Oct 1971 (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Cunningham, Dennis (Part 14 of 14): SF 100-70695, Nov 1971-Feb 1977 (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: Various Case Numbers, Oct 1971-Apr 1978 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References, 1969-1972 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References, 1969-1978 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References, 1970-1975 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References, 1970-1977 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References [I], 1970-1978 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References [II], 1978-1979 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References, 1971-1976 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References, 1971-1977 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References, 1972-1976 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References, 1973-1977 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Cunningham, Dennis: See References, 1974-1977 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Davis, Hugh M. (Part 1 of 2): HQ 157-26589, Aug 1972-Apr 1973 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Hugh M. (Part 1 of 2): DE 4-34, Aug 1972-May 1974 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Hugh M. (Part 2 of 2): Various Case Numbers, Jun 1970-Jul 1975 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Hugh M.: See References, 1971-1975 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Hugh M.: See References, 1972 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Dawley, Edward (Part 1 of 1): Various Case Numbers, May 1965-Jun 1971 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - Devaney, John: See References, 1971-1975 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Dickerson, Earl: Chicago Field Office 100-3299, File #40f [I], Apr 1955-May 1972 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Dickerson, Earl: Chicago Field Office 100-3299, File #40f [II], Apr 1955-May 1972 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Dickerson, Earl (Part 1 of 3): HQ 100-45805, Vol. 1, Oct 1941-Nov 1953 (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - Dickerson, Earl (Part 2 of 3): HQ 100-45805, Vol. 2, Nov 1953-Nov 1960 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - Dickerson, Earl (Part 3 of 3): HQ 100-45805, Vol. 3, Nov 1961-Apr 1969 (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - Dickerson, Earl: HQ 100-45805, Vol.1, Oct 1941-Oct 1953 (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - Dickerson, Earl: HQ 100-45804, Vol. 2, Nov 1953-Nov 1957 (Box 154, Folder 22)
    - Dickerson, Earl: HQ 100-45804, Vol. 2, Nov 1957-Nov 1960 (Box 154, Folder 23)
    - Dickerson, Earl: HQ 100-45804, Vol. 3, Nov 1961-Dec 1963 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Dickerson, Earl: HQ 100-45804, Vol. 3, Feb 1964-Apr 1969 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Dickerson, Earl (Part 1 of 2): HQ 161-125, Vol. 1, Dec 1960-Feb 1961 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Dickerson, Earl (Part 1 of 2): HQ 161-125, Vol. 1, Mar 1961 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Dickerson, Earl (Part 2 of 2): Various Case Numbers, Jan 1961-Sep 1963 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References, 1929-1967 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References, 1938-1961 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References, 1939-1964 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References [I], 1941-1956 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References [II], 1941-1956 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References [I], 1941-1958 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References [II], 1941-1958 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References [I], 1941-1964 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References [II], 1941-1964 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References [I], 1941-1965 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References [II], 1941-1965 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References, 1941-1974 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References, 1941-1983 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References, 1942-1969 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References, 1943-1950 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References, 1943-1983 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Dickerson, Earl: See References, 1944-1955 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - DiSuvero, Henry (Part 1 of 6): HQ 44-39171 [I], 1968 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - DiSuvero, Henry (Part 1 of 6): HQ 44-39171 [II], 1968 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - DiSuvero, Henry (Part 2 of 6): HQ 44-79407 and HQ 100-450317, 1977-1979 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - DiSuvero, Henry (Part 3 of 6): NY 100-163130, Vols. 1 and 2, 1968 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - DiSuvero, Henry (Part 4 of 6): NY 100-163130, Vol. 3, and NY 157-8912 [I], 1969-1972 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - DiSuvero, Henry (Part 4 of 6): NY 100-163130, Vol. 3, and NY 157-8912 [II], 1969-1972 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - DiSuvero, Henry (Part 5 of 6): LA 100-81174, Vols. 1 and 2, and LA 44-3576 [I], 1973-1978 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - DiSuvero, Henry (Part 5 of 6): LA 100-81174, Vols. 1 and 2, and LA 44-3576 [II], 1973-1978 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - DiSuvero, Henry (Part 6 of 6): Various Case Numbers, 1955-1972 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - DiSuvero, Henry: See References, 1965-1973 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - DiSuvero, Henry: See References, 1965-1974 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - DiSuvero, Henry: See References, 1968-1976 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 1 of 2): Various Case Numbers, Mar 1970-Aug 1975 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 2 of 2): Various Case Numbers, Apr 1969-Jan 1973 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 1 of 22): HQ 100-450008, Vol. 1, Jun 1968-Jun 1969 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 2 of 22): HQ 100-450008, Vol. 2, Jun 1969-Jul 1969 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 2 of 22): HQ 100-450008, Vol. 2, Jul 1969-Feb 1970 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 3 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Aug 1968-Feb 1970 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 4 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Jul 1967-Jan 1970 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 5 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vols. 2 and 3, Aug 1968-Dec 1968 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 6 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vols. 4 and 5, Dec 1968-Mar 1969 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 7 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 6, Feb 1969-Apr 1969 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 7 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 7, Apr 1969-May 1969 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 8 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 8, May 1969-Jun 1969 (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 9 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 9, Jun 1969 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 9 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 9, Jul 1969 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 10 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 10, Jul 1969 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 10 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 11, Jul 1969 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 11 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 12, Jul 1969-Aug 1969 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 12 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 13, Aug 1969-Sep 1969 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 13 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 14, Sep 1969-Oct 1969 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 13 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 14, Oct 1969-Nov 1969 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 14 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 15, Nov 1969 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 14 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 15, Nov 1969-Jan 1970 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 15 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 16, Jan 1970-Feb 1970 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 15 of 22): CG 100-45568, Vol. 17, Feb 1968-Mar 1970 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 16 of 22): CG 176-1103, Vol. 1, Sep 1968-Dec 1969 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 16 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Aug 1968-Jan 1970 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 17 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Sep 1968-Mar 1970 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 17 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Feb 1969-Nov 1969 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 18 of 22): Various Case Numbers [I], Aug 1968-Mar 1970 (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 18 of 22): Various Case Numbers [II], Aug 1968-Mar 1970 (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 19 of 22): NY 100-161433, Vol. 1, Oct 1967-Apr 1970 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 19 of 22): NY 176-86, Aug 1969-Mar 1970 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 20 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Oct 1968-Mar 1970 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 20 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Oct 1968-Jan 1970 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 21 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Aug 1968-Mar 1970 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 21 of 22): SF 100-61415, Vol. 1, May 1969-Mar 1970 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 22 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Dec 1968-Mar 1970 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 22 of 22): Various Case Numbers, Oct 1968-Mar 1970 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine (Part 1 of 1): CG 100-45568, Vol. 8, Undated (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Dohrn, Bernardine: MEX 100-3080, Oct 1968-Sep 1969 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: HQ 100-52843 Section 1, Nov 1941-Feb 1952 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: HQ 100-52843 Section 2, Mar 1953-Jun 1953 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: HQ 100-52843 Section 2, Jul 1959-Aug 1962 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: HQ 100-52843 Section 3, Oct 1962-Feb 1976 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: HQ 100-52843, Nov 1941-Feb 1952 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: HQ 100-52843, Mar 1952-May 1964 (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: HQ 100-52843, Oct 1962-Feb 1976 (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: SF 100-5542, Jul 1941-Sep 1951 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: SF 100-5542, Nov 1951-Jan 1955 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: SF 100-5542, May 1955-Jan 1958 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: SF 100-5542, Jan 1958-Jan 1962 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: SF 100-5542, Mar 1962-Oct 1964 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: SF 100-5542, Dec 1964-Oct 1968 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: SF 100-5542, Jan 1969-Mar 1973 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: SF 100-5542 EBF, May 1941-Jun 1963 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: See References, 1943-1974 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: See References, 1947-1956 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: See References, 1954 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: See References, 1962-1974 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Dreyfus, Benjamin: See References, 1969 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Durr, Clifford (Part 1 of 4): HQ 101-1710, Vols. 1 and 2, Sep 1941-Feb 1949 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - Durr, Clifford (Part 1 of 4): HQ 101-1710, Vols. 1 and 2, Jul 1949-Apr 1951 (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Durr, Clifford (Part 2 of 4): HQ 101-1710, Vols. 3 and 4 Sub A, May 1951-Apr 1974 (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Durr, Clifford (Part 1 of 10): HQ 101-1710, EBF 129, 1974 (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Durr, Clifford (Part 3 of 4): WFO 1910369, Vol. 1 Subs. 1 and 2, Jul 1941-May 1964 (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - Durr, Clifford (Part 4 of 4): Various Case Numbers, Jul 1954-Sep 1968 (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Durr, Clifford (Part 4 of 4): Various Case Numbers, Nov 1947-Sep 1968 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Durr, Clifford: See References, 1943-1969 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Durr, Clifford: See References, 1946-1972 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Durr, Clifford: See References, 1948-1954 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Durr, Clifford: See References, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Emerson, Thomas: HQ 77-11404, Jan 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Emerson, Thomas: HQ 101-3315, Section 1, Sep 1941-Mar 1949 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Emerson, Thomas: HQ 101-3315, Section 2, Mar 1949-Jun 1950 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Emerson, Thomas: HQ 101-3315, Section 3, Jun 1950-Apr 1951 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Emerson, Thomas: HQ 101-3315, Section 4, Apr 1951-Jan 1953 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Emerson, Thomas: HQ 101-3315, Section 5, Jan 1953-Jan 1958 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Emerson, Thomas: HQ 101-3315, Section 6, Feb 1958-Feb 1965 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Emerson, Thomas: HQ 101-3315, Section 7, Jun 1965-Aug 1976 (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Emerson, Thomas: HQ 101-3315, Sub A, Jul 1950-Apr 1956 (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1937-1967 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1940-1966 (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1940-1967 (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1940-1975 (Box 161, Folder 18)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1941-1965 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1941-1968 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References [I], 1941-1972 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References [II], 1941-1972 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References [I], 1941-1973 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References [II], 1941-1973 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References [III], 1941-1973 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References [IV], 1941-1973 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1942-1969 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1943-1975 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1948-1966 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1948-1972 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1949-1954 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, 1949-1971 (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Emerson, Thomas: See References, Undated (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - France, Royal (Part 1 of 6): HQ 100-15757, Feb 1923-Sep 1962 (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - France, Royal (Part 2 of 6): NY 100-111142, Vol. 1, Aug 1952-Dec 1954 (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - France, Royal (Part 3 of 6): NY 100-111142, Vol. 2, Dec 1954-Mar 1956 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - France, Royal (Part 3 of 6): NY 100-111142, Vol. 3, Mar 1956-Nov 1957 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - France, Royal (Part 4 of 6): NY 100-111142, Vol. 4, Nov 1957-Mar 1959 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - France, Royal (Part 4 of 6): NY 100-111142, Vol. 5, Apr 1959-Jun 1960 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - France, Royal (Part 5 of 6): NY 100-111142, Vol. 6, Oct 1960-Oct 1961 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - France, Royal (Part 5 of 6): NY 100-111142, Vols. 7 and 8, Nov 1961-Jan 1964 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - France, Royal (Part 6 of 6): Various Case Numbers, Jun 1952-Sep 1963 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - France, Royal: See References, 1923-1962 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - France, Royal: See References, 1925-1968 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - France, Royal: See References [I], 1941-1962 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - France, Royal: See References [II], 1941-1962 (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - France, Royal: See References, 1943-1962 (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - France, Royal: See References, 1944-1957 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - France, Royal: See References, 1952-1960 (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - France, Royal: See References, 1954-1962 (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - France, Royal: See References, 1958 (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - France, Royal: See References, 1963-1965 (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - Gibbs, Robert: See References, 1969-1975 (Box 163, Folder 18)
    - Gibbs, Robert: See References, 1975-1978 (Box 163, Folder 19)
    - Ginger, Ann: See References, 1946-1971 (Box 163, Folder 20)
    - Ginger, Ann: See References, 1952-1958 (Box 163, Folder 21)
    - Ginger, Ann: See References, 1959 (Box 163, Folder 22)
    - Ginger, Ann: See References, 1965-1972 (Box 163, Folder 23)
    - Gold, Sharon (Part 1 of 1): HQ 100-448039 and SF 100-56721, Sep 1967-Feb 1972 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Gold, Sharon (Part 1 of 1): SF 100-56721, May 1966-Feb 1973 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Gold, Sharon (Part 1 of 1): Various Case Numbers, May 1966-Aug 1966 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Gold, Sharon: See References, 1965-1973 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Gold, Sharon: See References, 1966-1970 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Goodman, Ernest: 100-6963, Section 1, 1940-1946 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Goodman, Ernest: 100-6963, Section 2, 1946-1965 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Goodman, Ernest: 100-6963, Section 3, 1965-1974 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Goodman, Ernest: See References, 1941-1946 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Goodman, Ernest: See References, 1941-1975 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Goodman, Ernest: See References, 1942-1975 (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Goodman, Ernest: See References, 1961-1973 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Goodman, Ernest: See References, Undated (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Gutknecht, John (Part 1 of 1): HQ 62-112153, Mar 1968-Aug 1979 (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Gutknecht, John (Part 1 of 1): Various Case Numbers, Jan 1942-Apr 1957 (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Gutknecht, John: See References, 1938-1955 (Box 164, Folder 16)
    - Gutknecht, John: See References, 1939-1961 (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Gutknecht, John: See References, 1941-1976 (Box 164, Folder 18)
    - Gutknecht, John: See References, 1942-1955 (Box 164, Folder 19)
    - Harris, Paul (Part 1 of 2): HQ 44-48404, Feb 1971-Jul 1974 (Box 164, Folder 20)
    - Harris, Paul (Part 2 of 2): Various Case Numbers, Jun 1965-Sep 1965 (Box 164, Folder 21)
    - Harris, Paul (Part 1 of 1): AT 100-7494, Jun 1968-Oct 1968 (Box 164, Folder 22)
    - Harris, Paul (Part 1 of 1): SV 100-5271, Jun 1968-Aug 1968 (Box 164, Folder 23)
    - Harris, Paul: See References, 1965-1972 (Box 164, Folder 24)
    - Harris, Paul: See References, 1974-1975 (Box 164, Folder 25)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 1 of 10): HQ 100-436106, Sep 1961-Oct 1968 (Box 164, Folder 26)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 1 of 10): HQ 100-436106, Mar 1964-Oct 1968 (Box 164, Folder 27)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 1 of 10): HQ 100-436106, EBF 44, Jun 1967 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 2 of 10): Various Case Numbers, Sep 1952-Aug 1969 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 3 of 10): NF 100-5602, Vol. 1, May 1961-Oct 1961 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 3 of 10): NF 100-5602, Vol. 1, Nov 1961-Jan 1962 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 4 of 10): NF 100-5602, Vol. 2, Jan 1962-Jun 1962 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 4 of 10): NF 100-5602, Vol. 2, Jul 1962-Mar 1963 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 5 of 10): Vols. 3 and 4, Mar 1963-Nov 1965 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 6 of 10): WFO 100-39429, Vol. 1, Jul 1961-Jan 1964 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 6 of 10): WFO 100-39429, Vol. 2, Feb 1964-Jun 1964 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 7 of 10): WFO 100-39429, Vols. 3 - 5, Sep 1964-Feb 1969 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 8 of 10): SF 100-50364, Vol. 1, Jun 1962-Sep 1968 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 8 of 10): SF 100-39429, Vol. 2, Sep 1968-Jan 1973 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 9 of 10): CG 100-21960, Jun 1950-Mar 1963 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 9 of 10): NY 100-146999, May 1961-Jul 1967 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Holt, Leonard (Part 10 of 10): Various Case Numbers, Jul 1961-Jul 1968 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Holt, Leonard: See References, 1953-1978 (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Holt, Leonard: See References, 1958-1969 (Box 165, Folder 17)